I feel like we are in a world now that is so processed and is manufacturing so much that it is now also manufacturing hate.
It literally creates hate from out of thin air.
And there's so much hurt and trauma that hasn't been dealt with.
And baby, all of that energy exists.
Just so we're clear, energy is a real thing.
It's like when you stand next to a piano and you can feel the sound of the piano hitting you.
That's energy.
When you're in a room and someone walks in the room and it just rubs you the wrong way, that's energy.
Now, by the way, that energy might be your energy.
The rubbing the wrong way might be the fact that your energy is off.
So I just want to say that.
But energy is a real thing.
We are combusting.
We are made of atoms, y'all.
Your heart beating is an engine.
Like when you look at a car engine, it's the same as a body.
All of these pieces need to work together to make this thing move.
We are in a world where the energy is so processed with hate and mendacity and just negative things that some of our spirits literally can't process the energy.